1	1920	1920	CD	DATE	_	_
2	Mar	Mar	NNP	DATE	_	_
3	4	4	CD	DATE	_	_
4	pm	pm	NN	O	_	_
5	12	12	CD	NUMBER	_	_
6	23	23	CD	NUMBER	_	_
7	NEWYORK	NEWYORK	NNP	ORGANIZATION	_	_
8	NY	NY	NNP	STATE_OR_PROVINCE	_	_
9	Miss	Miss	NNP	STATE_OR_PROVINCE	_	_
10	Julia	Julia	NNP	O	_	_
11	Morgan	Morgan	NNP	O	_	_
12	Merchants	Merchants	NNPS	O	_	_
13	Exchange	Exchange	NNP	O	_	_
14	Bldg	Bldg	NNP	O	_	_
15	SANFRANCISCO	SANFRANCISCO	NNP	LOCATION	_	_
16	Calif	Calif	NNP	STATE_OR_PROVINCE	_	_
17	the	the	DT	O	_	_
18	plan	plan	NN	O	_	_
19	for	for	IN	O	_	_
20	improving	improve	VBG	O	_	_
21	view	view	NN	O	_	_
22	side	side	NN	O	_	_
23	of	of	IN	O	_	_
24	Bungalow	bungalow	NN	O	_	_
25	B	b	NN	O	_	_
26	is	be	VBZ	O	_	_
27	something	something	NN	O	_	_
28	similar	similar	JJ	O	_	_
29	to	to	TO	O	_	_
30	plan	plan	VB	O	_	_
31	for	for	IN	O	_	_
32	improving	improve	VBG	O	_	_
33	C	c	NN	O	_	_
34	which	which	WDT	O	_	_
35	I	I	PRP	O	_	_
36	have	have	VBP	O	_	_
37	lately	lately	RB	O	_	_
38	telegraphed	telegraph	VBN	O	_	_
39	it	it	PRP	O	_	_
40	contemplates	contemplate	VBZ	O	_	_
41	putting	put	VBG	O	_	_
42	an	a	DT	O	_	_
43	open	open	JJ	O	_	_
44	porch	porch	NN	O	_	_
45	before	before	IN	O	_	_
46	sittingroom	sittingroom	NN	O	_	_
47	on	on	IN	O	_	_
48	view	view	NN	O	_	_
49	side	side	NN	O	_	_
50	8	8	CD	NUMBER	_	_
51	or	or	CC	O	_	_
52	10	10	CD	NUMBER	_	_
53	feet	foot	NNS	O	_	_
54	deept	deept	NN	O	_	_
55	also	also	RB	O	_	_
56	deepening	deepen	VBG	O	_	_
57	porches	porch	NNS	O	_	_
58	before	before	IN	O	_	_
59	bedrooms	bedroom	NNS	O	_	_
60	so	so	IN	O	_	_
61	that	that	IN	O	_	_
62	they	they	PRP	O	_	_
63	reach	reach	VBP	O	_	_
64	forward	forward	RB	O	_	_
65	to	to	TO	O	_	_
66	one	one	CD	NUMBER	_	_
67	half	half	PDT	O	_	_
68	the	the	DT	O	_	_
69	depth	depth	NN	O	_	_
70	of	of	IN	O	_	_
71	the	the	DT	O	_	_
72	central	central	JJ	O	_	_
73	porch	porch	NN	O	_	_
74	then	then	RB	O	_	_
75	have	have	VBP	O	_	_
76	stairs	stair	NNS	O	_	_
77	descend	descend	VB	O	_	_
78	from	from	IN	O	_	_
79	each	each	DT	O	_	_
80	side	side	NN	O	_	_
81	of	of	IN	O	_	_
82	Centra	Centra	NNP	ORGANIZATION	_	_
83	Porch	Porch	NNP	ORGANIZATION	_	_
84	and	and	CC	O	_	_
85	before	before	RB	O	_	_
86	.	.	.	O	_	_

1	Side	side	NN	O	_	_
2	porches	porch	NNS	O	_	_
3	doubling	double	VBG	O	_	_
4	back	back	RP	O	_	_
5	before	before	IN	O	_	_
6	central	central	JJ	O	_	_
7	porch	porch	NN	O	_	_
8	after	after	IN	O	_	_
9	manner	manner	NN	O	_	_
10	of	of	IN	O	_	_
11	staircase	staircase	NN	O	_	_
12	in	in	IN	O	_	_
13	Cathedral	cathedral	NN	O	_	_
14	of	of	IN	O	_	_
15	Burgos	Burgos	NNP	CITY	_	_
16	the	the	DT	O	_	_
17	Escalera	Escalera	NNP	ORGANIZATION	_	_
18	Doroda	Doroda	NNP	ORGANIZATION	_	_
19	big	big	JJ	O	_	_
20	decorative	decorative	JJ	O	_	_
21	door	door	NN	O	_	_
22	below	below	IN	O	_	_
23	into	into	IN	O	_	_
24	lower	lower	JJR	O	_	_
25	room	room	NN	O	_	_
26	and	and	CC	O	_	_
27	terrace	terrace	NN	O	_	_
28	garden	garden	NN	O	_	_
29	supported	support	VBN	O	_	_
30	by	by	IN	O	_	_
31	concrete	concrete	JJ	O	_	_
32	walls	wall	NNS	O	_	_
33	and	and	CC	O	_	_
34	rail	rail	NN	O	_	_
35	in	in	IN	O	_	_
36	front	front	NN	O	_	_
37	of	of	IN	O	_	_
38	course	course	NN	O	_	_
39	the	the	DT	O	_	_
40	deepened	deepen	VBN	O	_	_
41	upper	upper	JJ	O	_	_
42	side	side	NN	O	_	_
43	porches	porch	NNS	O	_	_
44	might	might	MD	O	_	_
45	be	be	VB	O	_	_
46	loggias	loggia	NNS	O	_	_
47	or	or	CC	O	_	_
48	the	the	DT	O	_	_
49	added	add	VBN	O	_	_
50	central	central	JJ	O	_	_
51	porches	porch	NNS	O	_	_
52	on	on	IN	O	_	_
53	Bungalow	bungalow	NN	O	_	_
54	B	b	NN	O	_	_
55	and	and	CC	O	_	_
56	to	to	TO	O	_	_
57	have	have	VB	O	_	_
58	central	central	JJ	O	_	_
59	convered	conver	VBN	O	_	_
60	Loggia	Loggia	NNP	PERSON	_	_
61	only	only	RB	O	_	_
62	on	on	IN	O	_	_
63	House	House	NNP	ORGANIZATION	_	_
64	c	c	NN	O	_	_
65	the	the	DT	O	_	_
66	outside	outside	JJ	O	_	_
67	stairs	stair	NNS	O	_	_
68	for	for	IN	O	_	_
69	House	House	NNP	ORGANIZATION	_	_
70	C	c	NN	O	_	_
71	should	should	MD	O	_	_
72	be	be	VB	O	_	_
73	like	like	IN	O	_	_
74	those	those	DT	O	_	_
75	of	of	IN	O	_	_
76	house	house	NN	O	_	_
77	a	a	DT	O	_	_
78	and	and	CC	O	_	_
79	not	not	RB	O	_	_
80	like	like	VB	O	_	_
81	those	those	DT	O	_	_
82	of	of	IN	O	_	_
83	House	House	NNP	ORGANIZATION	_	_
84	b	b	NN	O	_	_
85	hope	hope	NN	O	_	_
86	this	this	DT	O	_	_
87	is	be	VBZ	O	_	_
88	clear	clear	JJ	O	_	_
89	W	w	NN	O	_	_
90	R	r	NN	O	_	_
91	hearst	hearst	NN	O	_	_
92	.	.	.	O	_	_

